No 80 Jalan Tas 8, Taman Tas, Jalan Gambang, 25150 Kuantan Pahang

02 Oktober 2020

#### FAR EAST HOLDINGS BERHAD

Level 23, Menara Zenith, Jalan Putra Square 6, 25200 Kuantan, Pahang Darul Makmur

Dear Sir,

I would like to apply for the post as an **Internal Audit Executive** in your institution to enhance my knowledge and acquired new experience.

I graduated from University of Malaya with a **Degree in Accounting** on May 2009 and also member of **Malaysian Institute of Accountants (MIA)**. Currently, I am working at Pahang Corporation Sdn Bhd as Senior Account Executive. Previously I am working at Rumpun Timur Sdn Bhd (wholly-owned subsidiary of Perbadanan Kemajuan Negeri Pahang) as an Account Executive. However, working for your company appeals to me because of strong reputation and provide excellent practice.

During my internships at the Perbadanan Kemajuan Negeri Pahang and Wan Nadzir & Co., Kuantan, I dealt with various account transactions and such experiences allowed me to learn important skills and to develop the confidence needed to succeed in a competitive environment.

I am a motivated and independent individual who can easily adapt into new situations with a creative and resourceful attitude and therefore, I am so enthusiastic in extending my best services and hoping that I can contribute with my proficiency and my ability to work cooperatively in your organization.

I would be grateful if you could give me an opportunity for an interview according to your convenience time.

Thank You.

Yours Faithfully #ASRUMA

(Hasruma binti Alias) Enclose:

Resume

Passport size photo



HASRUMA BINTI ALIAS NO 80 JALAN TAS 8 TAMAN TAS JALAN GAMBANG 25150 KUANTAN PAHANG H/P: 012-9575038

E-MAIL: hasrumaalias@yahoo.com

#### **OBJECTIVE**

To obtain a challenging position in **Internal Audit Executive** field that offer extensive learning and opportunities growth.

## **ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS**

• Member of Malaysian Institute of Accountants (MIA)

CA Number: 40411

• University of Malaya, Kuala Lumpur

4 July 2005 - 2 May 2009 Bachelor in Accounting

CGPA: 2.50/ 4.00

• Politeknik Sultan Haji Ahmad Shah, Kuantan

1 December 2001- 22 December 2004 Program: Accounting

CGPA: 3.24/ 4.00

• Malaysian University English Test (MUET)

Band: 3/6

• Sekolah Menengah Teknik Seri Pelindung, Kuantan

23 February 1999 - 31 December 2000

SPM: 2A's

• Sek. Men. Keb. Paya Besar, Kuantan

2 January 1996 - 22 February 1999

PMR: 2A's

#### **WORKING EXPERIENCES**

Date : 16 March 2020 – Present (Senior Account Executive)
Department : Finance Department, **Pahang Corporation Sdn Bhd** 

Job Descriptions : Prepare full set of accounts, account console and yearly

budget for the group of company, bank reconciliation,

payments for suppliers, report of budget and others.

Date : 18 April 2010 – 15 March 2020 (Account Executive)

Department : Finance Department, **Rumpun Timur Sdn Bhd** 

Job Descriptions : Prepare full set of accounts, bank reconciliation, payments

for suppliers, report of budget and others.

Date : 5 May 2008 - 11 July 2008 (Industrial Training)

Department : Finance Department,

Perbadanan Kemajuan Negeri Pahang

Job Descriptions : To record various transactions for different departments

such as receipts and payments, finance, claims and

payroll.

Date : 6 June 2003 - 31 July 2003 (Industrial Training)
Department : Audit and Tax Departments, **Wan Nadzir & Co** 

Job Descriptions : Learn how to do vouching and sampling, amending draft

audited report, bank reconciliation.

# **STRENGTHS**

1. Pleasant persenality and good in communication as well as collaboration skills.

2. Responsible and hardworking.

3. Self-motivated, resourceful and able to work independently.

4. Excellent computer literate.

## **EXCELELNT SKILLS**

Language : Fluent in Malay Language and English Languages.

Computer : Proficient in Ms Office (Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel and Microsoft

PowerPoint), User Business System (UBS), ACCPAC accounting system

and Biztrak accounting system.

#### **CO-CURRICULUM ACTIVITIES**

#### UNIVERSITY OF MALAYA, KUALA LUMPUR

- Participated in ACCA-UM Construct Workshop 2008
- Handball player for the Sukan Mahasiswa Universiti Malaya for 2 years
- Secretary for Malam Penganugerahan Astar Fasa 1
- Secretary for Sukaneka
- Secretary for Debat Terbuka Astar
- Volunteer for Debat Terbuka Astar
- Participated in Astar Scrabble Challenge Inter-College 2006/2007

#### SEKOLAH MENENGAH TEKNIK SERI PELINDUNG, KUANTAN

• Participated in science and mathematics festival for Kuantan district

# SEKOLAH MENENGAH PAYA BESAR, KUANTAN

• Participated for Pahang Pandu Puteri camping 1997

## **TRAININGS**

# • Take Charge!

Date : 4 August 2006

Venue : Faculty of Built Environment, University of Malaya

## ACCA- UM Construct Workshop 2007

Date: 23 February 2007

Venue : Faculty of Business and Accountancy, University of Malaya

## • Goods and Services Tax (GST) Workshop

Date : 27th - 28th October 2014

Venue : EDC Level 3, Kompleks Teruntum

# Seminar "GST dan Perlaksanaannya" anjuran Kastam bersama Notice A Association

# Norila & Associates

Date: 17th November 2014

Venue : Hotel Grand Continental, Kuantan

# An Overview of MPERS in 2016 – Including the 2015 Amendments

Date : 08/03/2016

Venue: TH Hotel & Convention Centre, Kuala Terengganu

#### **AWARDS**

## UNIVERSITY OF MALAYA, KUALA LUMPUR

• 4th place for handball (Sukan Mahasiswa Universiti Malaya)

## SEKOLAH MENENGAH PAYA BESAR, KUANTAN

• 3<sup>rd</sup> place for Choral Speaking Competition (English week 14-16 April 1997)

## **EXPECTED REMUNERATION**

Expected remuneration: RM 5,500.00 (Negotiable)

Current remuneration: RM 5,300.00

#### **PERSONAL DETAILS**

Age : 37 Years Old Date of birth : 25 April 1983

Place of birth : Besut, Terengganu
Identity Card number : 830425-11-5552
Nationality : Malaysian
Marital status : Single
Religion : Islam
Race : Malay

Gender : Female

## **REFERENCE**

Puan Norlela binti Mohd Rais Company Sectary, Bangunan Tanah Makmur Berhad KotaSAS Avenue, Jalan Kota SAS, Kota Sultan Ahmad Shah, 25200 Kuantan.

20200 Roaman.

H/P No.: 019-3800880